<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/xml" href="/feed.xslt.xml"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><generator uri="http://jekyllrb.com" version="3.3.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-08-27T14:48:55-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/</id><title>Li Annan | Something Brilliant This Way Comes</title><subtitle>It‘s my personal page.
</subtitle><author><name>Li Annan</name><email>lian16@mails.tsinghua.edu.com</email></author><entry><title>Honors</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2018/12/08/3-Honor/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Honors" /><published>2018-12-08T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2018-12-08T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2018/12/08/3-Honor</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2018/12/08/3-Honor/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/fulls/honors2.jpg&quot; class=&quot;fit image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;scholarship&quot;&gt;Scholarship&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;“December 9th” Outstanding Scholarship in Overall Aspect  (Highest Scholarship for Freshman in Tsinghua)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Distinguished Student Leader of Tsinghua University&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;University Scholarship for Outstanding Social Work&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;University Scholarship for Outstanding Artistic Work&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;University Scholarship for Outstanding Technological Innovation&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;University Scholarship for Outstanding Social Investigation&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;University Scholarship for Outstanding Voluntary&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;HAGE Scholarship of Automation Department&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;honors-as-innovator&quot;&gt;Honors as Innovator&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;As first author, awarded as Meritorious Winner in MCM/ICM2019 (February, 2019)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;As first author, ranked 3th in &lt;em&gt;The 7th Innovation Competition of Tsinghua University&lt;/em&gt;  (May, 2018)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;As first author, won third Prize in &lt;em&gt;The 36th Challenge Cup of Tsinghua University&lt;/em&gt; (April, 2018)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;As team member, ranking 4th in &lt;em&gt;The 2th Microsoft-Tsinghua Digital Reality Development Competition&lt;/em&gt; (December, 2017)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;As team leader, won 2nd Prize in &lt;em&gt;Hardware Design Competition of Tsinghua University&lt;/em&gt; (June, 2017)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;honors-as-volunteer&quot;&gt;Honors as Volunteer&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;International Volunteer of &lt;em&gt;World Without Borders&lt;/em&gt; Program (February, 2018)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Excellent Volunteer of &lt;em&gt;The 15th Buddy Program&lt;/em&gt; (December, 2017)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Three Star Volunteers of Tsinghua University (June, 2017)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;First Prize of &lt;em&gt;The 15th Return to Alma Mater Program of Tsinghua University&lt;/em&gt; (May, 2017)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;honors-as-athlete&quot;&gt;Honors as Athlete&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Ranking 5th in &lt;em&gt;Group Taiji Competition of Tsinghua&lt;/em&gt; (As team leader) (December, 2017)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Ranking 5th in &lt;em&gt;Men’s Taiji Competition of Tsinghua&lt;/em&gt; (December,2017)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Fighting Spirit Award of Automation Department (June, 2017)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Accomplish Award of &lt;em&gt;The Campus Marathon of Tsinghua&lt;/em&gt; (10km) (April, 2017)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Ranking 4th in &lt;em&gt;Aerobics Competition of Tsinghua&lt;/em&gt;  (April, 2017)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Ranking first in &lt;em&gt;Freshmen’s Skipping and Running Competition of Tsinghua&lt;/em&gt; (November, 2016)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name>Li Annan</name><email>lian16@mails.tsinghua.edu.com</email></author><summary>Scholarship</summary></entry><entry><title>Academic Experience</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2018/12/08/2-Academic/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Academic Experience" /><published>2018-12-08T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2018-12-08T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2018/12/08/2-Academic</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2018/12/08/2-Academic/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/fulls/Tsinghua.jpg&quot; class=&quot;fit image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;education-experience&quot;&gt;Education Experience&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;major--automation-eecs&quot;&gt;Major : Automation (EECS)&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;August, 2016  ~  present&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Major in Department of Automation, Tsinghua University, Beijing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GPA：3.73/4    Rank: 24/168   (3 years)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Course Title&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Grade&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Course Title&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Grade&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Calculus A(1)&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A-&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Fundamentals of Engineering Graphics&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A-&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Linear Algebra(1)&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A-&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Linear Algebra(2)&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A-&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Numerical Analysis and Algorithms&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A-&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Operations Research&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Physics for Scientists and Engineers B(1)&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A-&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Physics for Scientists and Engineers B(2)&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Computer Languages and Programming&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Data Structures&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A-&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Computer Networks and Applications&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A-&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Principle of Circuits&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A-&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Measurement Principle&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A-&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Linear Control Systems Engineering&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A-&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mathematics:&lt;/strong&gt; Calculus A(2), Introduction to Complex Analysis, Stocastic Mathematical Methods, Signals and System Analysis, Numerical Analysis and Algorithms, Principle of Automatic Control, Operations Research, .&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Computer Science:&lt;/strong&gt; C++ Programme Design and Training, Computer Networks and Applications, Digital Image Processing, Fundamental Pattern Recognition.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Electrical Courses：&lt;/strong&gt;Digital Electronics, Fundamentals of Analog Electronics, Contemporary Electronic System Design, Foundamentals of Power Electronics Technology, Linear Control Systems Engineering, Electrical Driver and Motion Control System.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Others:&lt;/strong&gt; Computational Genome Analysis, Introduction of Terahertz Techonology, Dialogue between Neuroscience and Artificial Intelligence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;research-experience&quot;&gt;Research Experience&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;robocup2019&quot;&gt;RoboCup2019&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;September, 2018 ~ July, 2019&lt;br /&gt;Supervised by Associate Prof. &lt;em&gt;Mingguo Zhao&lt;/em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;,&lt;/strong&gt; Institute of Control Theory and Technology, Tsinghua University.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Index terms: Robotics, Localization, SLAM&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our team participated in the RobotCup2019, Sydney and won three awards in AdultSize competition of Humanoid League of RoboCup 2019, including &lt;em&gt;Second Place of Technical Challenge&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Second Place of Drop-in Competition&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Third Place of 2v2 Soccer Match.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Based on the robot from last year, our major improvement includes faster and more stable
visual detection and motion gait algorithm. As a member of &lt;em&gt;Vision Detection Group&lt;/em&gt; of our team, I mainly focused on the work of self-locationing algorithm based on vision input. By recognizing certain landmarks, like goal post and special point in the field, our new self-locationing algorithm has achieved more accurate and reliable results, decresing the drift error of INS system.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/fulls/RoboCup.jpg&quot; class=&quot;fit image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;newbalance-transportation-scooter&quot;&gt;NewBalance: Transportation Scooter&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;February, 2019 ~ June, 2019&lt;br /&gt;Supervised by &lt;em&gt;Prof. Qianchuan Zhao&lt;/em&gt;, Center for Intelligent and Networked Systems, Tsinghua University, and &lt;em&gt;Associate Prof.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;Mingguo Zhao&lt;/em&gt;, Institute of Control Theory and Technology,  Tsinghua University&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Index terms: Control Theory, Mathematical and Physical Simulation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Adopting a PID controller, our goal is to achieve a stable self-balance result with adaptive ability to different payload. With reasonable abstraction, we developed a mathematical model and conducted simulation using Simulink on Matlab to find the best parameter sets and then built a physical model using Simscape on Matlab to narrow the theoretical feasible domain. Finally, a real scooter is assembled to achieve the transportation function.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dropbox.com/s/5fq81riu66fymc4/NewBalance.mp4?dl=0&quot;&gt;Click to watch the video:&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/fulls/NewBalance.jpg&quot; class=&quot;fit image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;an-enhenced-indoor-positioning-method-without-extra-deploying-devices&quot;&gt;An Enhenced Indoor Positioning Method without Extra Deploying Devices&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;December, 2018 ~ present&lt;br /&gt;Supervised by Associate Prof. &lt;em&gt;Qinshan Jia&lt;/em&gt;, Center for Intelligent and Network System,  Tsinghua University.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Index terms: Indoor Positioning, Inertial Navigation, Augmented Reality&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Current indoor positioning methods are not practical especially in emergency cases, because they require deploying a large number of devices within the buildings, like RFID or routers. In order to solve the existed problem, we proposes a positioning method that fuses the data from inertial navigation system, floor plans of buildings and the distributed data of the evacuation signs. This positioning method achieves the required precision with no need for deploying extra devices in the buildings. &lt;br /&gt;We adopts particle filter to implement the positioning method. Matlab is used to simulate the process of observing, calculating and positioning with the real world data collected from the FIT building of Tsinghua . The results  have proved our method effective in reducing the position error. We are now attending to apply the method to real-world use, developping a HoloLens project with Unity3D. If we can demonstrate the feasibility of this positioning method, it can be utilized in some emergency cases, like assisting the fireman to navigate in fire area.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/fulls/position1.png&quot; class=&quot;fit image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;hawkeye-skyguard--intelligent-aerial-patrol-robot&quot;&gt;Hawkeye Skyguard:  Intelligent Aerial Patrol Robot&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Augest, 2018  ~  February, 2019&lt;br /&gt;Supervised by Lectuer &lt;em&gt;Yipeng Li&lt;/em&gt;, Institute of Control Theory and Technology, Tsinghua University.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Index terms: Aerial Robot Control,  Pedestrian Detection, Action Detection&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This project aims to build a Police Intelligent UAV to solve the problem that there is not enough Moblie Police Force in remote part of cities. Our Intelligent UAV has three main functions: Autonomous Cruise、Detection of Violence and Object Tracking and Alarm.&lt;br /&gt;The UAV will cruise over the street according to the prescribed route with ability to avoid dynamic and static obstacles. Once it detect violent behavior of a person by its camera using computer vision method, it will track the object in the sky and alarm the police simultaneously. Besides, it can carry some expulsion weapons like strong light and loudspeaker to warn and Prevent crimes.&lt;br /&gt;This project has passed the &lt;em&gt;University Students Innovation and Entrepreneurship Project of Beijing&lt;/em&gt; and won the  financial support.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/fulls/drone.png&quot; class=&quot;fit image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;transglass-personal-assistant-in-foreign-language-environment&quot;&gt;TransGlass: Personal Assistant in Foreign Language Environment&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;December, 2017  ~  May, 2018  (as team leader)&lt;br /&gt;Supervised by Associate Prof. &lt;em&gt;Qinshan Jia&lt;/em&gt;, Center for Intelligent and Network System,  Tsinghua University.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Index terms: Character Translation, Augmented Reality&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Transglass is a project developed on HoloLens with Unity3D, aiming to solve the problem that people can not figure out what the words means in other languages. We choose two main usage seenarios , international study and international traveling, and also develop special function to serve the international students or tranveler respectively.&lt;br /&gt; In the demo version, the Chinese words in the sight will be translated into English automatically and replace the original words in AR method. In the student mode, the Chinese slides can be translated into English version and display on the wall nearby which can adjusted easily. And in the traveller mode, the Chinese sign will be translated.&lt;br /&gt;Apart from translation, we have also provided 3D teaching model for the class situation, making it much easier for students to understand a 3D object and learn better. For international travellers, after the Chinese words are translated into English, a searching button can be touched. If do so, a screen will pop up in the sight, linking to the Wekipedia title of the translated text’s key word. Another function is Virtual Message Box, which means you can leave any personal message in a famous scenery. In this way, we can tackle the problem that some people tend to scrawl even on some historical relics.&lt;br /&gt;TransGlass has won Third Prize in &lt;em&gt;The 36th Challenge Cup of Tsinghua University&lt;/em&gt; (2018.4) and  3rd place in &lt;em&gt;The 7th Innovation Competition of Tsinghua University&lt;/em&gt; (2018.5)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dropbox.com/s/herr191n7nm9tvb/TransGlass.mp4?dl=0&quot;&gt;Click to watch the video:&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/images/fulls/transclass.png&quot; heigh=&quot;80%&quot; width=&quot;80%&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/images/fulls/transglass2.jpg&quot; heigh=&quot;80%&quot; width=&quot;80%&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;intelligent-fire-rescure-helmet&quot;&gt;Intelligent Fire Rescure Helmet&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;October, 2017  ~  December, 2017 &lt;br /&gt;Supervised by Associate Prof. &lt;em&gt;Qinshan Jia&lt;/em&gt;, Center for Intelligent and Network System,  Tsinghua University.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Index terms:  Inertial Navigation ,Augmented Reality, Vision Enhancement&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Intellgent fire rescure helmet is a project developed on HoloLens on the purpose to assist the fireman to rescure the trapped personnel efficiently with two main functions. &lt;br /&gt;The first is navigation.In the case that fire station have detected the layout of the building, the helmat will scan the environment and calculate where the fireman is and lead him to the location where the rescures called for help. The second function is visual field enhancement. The helmat will use infrared scanning to detect the surroundings and build the 3D environment model, helping the user to have a clear sight in the situation where lightness is not enough or the smoke is heavy.&lt;br /&gt;Our project won 4th place in &lt;em&gt;The 2th Microsoft-Tsinghua Digital Reality Development Competition&lt;/em&gt;(2017.12)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/fulls/Fire1.jpg&quot; heigh=&quot;80%&quot; width=&quot;80%&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;course-project&quot;&gt;Course Project&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Multi-view 3D Reconstruction of Human Body&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Data Structure, Supervised by Associate Prof. Yebin Liu&lt;br /&gt;Utilized Shape-from-Silhouette method to rebuild the Visual Hull of a human body from several pictures from different views.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;div align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/fulls/datastructure.png&quot; heigh=&quot;60%&quot; width=&quot;60%&quot; /&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Feature Extraction and Enhancement of Coronary Artery 3D Image&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Digtal Image Processing, Supervised by Prof. Jianjiang Feng&lt;br /&gt;The processing includes Center Line Extraction, Disconnected Repair and Model Construction.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;div align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/fulls/imageprogressing.png&quot; heigh=&quot;80%&quot; width=&quot;80%&quot; align=&quot;middle&quot; /&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Face Synthesis Based on Facial Features&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Numerical Analysis and Algorithms, Supervised by Prof. Jie Zhou&lt;br /&gt;Implemented facial image fusion function with TPS and B-Spline algorithm. Enhanced the fusing performance with several interpolation methods such as Bilinear Interpolation.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;div align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/fulls/Trump.png&quot; heigh=&quot;80%&quot; width=&quot;80%&quot; /&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;P2P Chat System Design&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Computer Networks and Applications, Supervised by Associate Prof. Qingshan Jia&lt;br /&gt;Designed a Peer-to-Peer Chat System for instant messaging based on a central location server.Used hybrid network architecture of C/S and P2P to query the current state of users and set up chat links.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;div align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/fulls/MeChat.png&quot; heigh=&quot;90%&quot; width=&quot;90%&quot; /&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;computing-skills-and-others&quot;&gt;COMPUTING SKILLS AND OTHERS&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Programming languages:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;​	C#, C, C++, Python, html, MATLAB, VerilogHDL, Assembly Language.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Software and Operation Systems:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;​	ROS, Unity3D, Unreal Engine, Autodesk Fuse, Ultimaker Cura, GitHub, Linux.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Languages:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;​	Native in Chinese; Proficient in English (TOFEL 100)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;special-talents-training-program-of-tsinghua&quot;&gt;Special Talents Training Program of Tsinghua&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;siyuan-leadership-program&quot;&gt;Siyuan Leadership Program&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;April, 2017  ~  present&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Member of 16th Siyuan Leadership Program  (36 selected from whole Tsinghua)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Under the idea of “receiving, growing and giving”,  “Siyuan” is an outstanding college student development program that is tailored to cultivate the future leaders with strong sense of social responsibility and the spirit to contribute.&lt;br /&gt;Every year’s summer social practice, Siyuan students are required to set up projects in fields like politics, economy and society and research on those projects through both literature review and field study. The themes for each year are “A feeling for motherland”, “Chinese power” and “International vision”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/fulls/Siyuan.jpg&quot; class=&quot;fit image&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Visiting &lt;em&gt;Phoenix Satellite TV&lt;/em&gt; in Hong Kong (August, 2018)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;qichuang-entrepreneurship-program&quot;&gt;Qichuang Entrepreneurship Program&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;June, 2018  ~  present&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Member of 6th Qichuang Entrepreneurship Program (20 selected from whole Tsinghua)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In Chinese, “Qi” means “start” and “Chuang” means “innovation”. So with these two main goals, “Qichuang Program” requires the elected students to be equipped with the ability of innovation and the courage to start. &lt;br /&gt;In winter vacation of 2019, we will make a trip to Y combinator in silicon valley and visit Standford University for a week to soak up  the the atmosphere of innovation and entrepreneurship. And we are provided with much related resources, like the opportunity to shadow a CEO of some start-ups for a week to learn how to lead a company to develop fast.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/fulls/Qichuang.jpg&quot; class=&quot;fit image&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Visiting &lt;em&gt;Stanford University&lt;/em&gt; in California (February, 2019)&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Li Annan</name><email>lian16@mails.tsinghua.edu.com</email></author><summary></summary></entry><entry><title>Extracurricular Life</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2018/12/08/1-Life/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Extracurricular Life" /><published>2018-12-08T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2018-12-08T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2018/12/08/1-Life</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2018/12/08/1-Life/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/fulls/brilliant.jpg&quot; class=&quot;fit image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;activity-organizer&quot;&gt;Activity Organizer&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;June, 2018  ~  June,2019&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Vice President of Student Union, in charge of Public Relations Department and Propaganda Department. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;February, 2018  ~  May, 2018&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Student Assistant at X-lab ( Innovation and Entrepreneurship Platform of Tsinghua)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;June, 2017  ~  June, 2018&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Minister of Public Relations Department of Student Union&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;May, 2017  ~  May, 2018&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Monitor of Class 63 of Automation Department&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;kung-fu-player&quot;&gt;Kung Fu Player&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Palyer of Yongchun &amp;amp; Taiji.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/fulls/taiji1.jpg&quot; class=&quot;fit image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Playing Taiji on the summit of Wudang Mountain, where Taiji originates from.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/fulls/taiji2.jpeg&quot; class=&quot;fit image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Being the captain of Wushu Team of Automation Department.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;diversified-athlete&quot;&gt;Diversified Athlete&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/fulls/Dive.jpg&quot; class=&quot;fit image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/fulls/Fence&amp;amp;Shoot.jpg&quot; class=&quot;fit image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;enthusiastic-volunteer&quot;&gt;Enthusiastic Volunteer&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/fulls/voluntary.png&quot; class=&quot;fit image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Voluntary Teaching in Huaqing High School, Shanxi Provice, China (August, 2017)&lt;br /&gt;Voluntary Work at Orphanage, Canggu, Indonesia (January, 2018)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/fulls/shuxiao.jpg&quot; class=&quot;fit image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Being Councellor in Summer School of Tsinghua University (July, 2017)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;confident-artist&quot;&gt;Confident Artist&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/fulls/host1.jpg&quot; class=&quot;fit image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Being the host of &lt;em&gt;Student Festival Literature and Art Evening&lt;/em&gt;. (December, 2017)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/fulls/dance1.jpg&quot; class=&quot;fit image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Orginizing &lt;em&gt;Freshman’s Dance Party&lt;/em&gt; (September, 2017)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;world-explorer&quot;&gt;World Explorer&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Travelling a lot, 77 cities in China, covering 22 provinces, and 8 countries in the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/fulls/Japan.jpg&quot; class=&quot;fit image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;June, 2018 @Tokyo, Japan&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/fulls/SF&amp;amp;LA.jpg&quot; class=&quot;fit image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;February, 2019 @San Francisco &amp;amp; Los Angeles&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/fulls/DC.jpg&quot; class=&quot;fit image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;July, 2019 @Washington DC&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;brave-hacker&quot;&gt;Brave Hacker&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/fulls/hackthon3.jpg&quot; class=&quot;fit image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;JUNCTIONxTsinghua&lt;/em&gt;, Beijing, China (May, 2018)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/fulls/hackthon4.jpg&quot; class=&quot;fit image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;TechX Hackthon&lt;/em&gt;, Shanghai, China (August, 2018)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;practical-entrepreneur&quot;&gt;Practical Entrepreneur&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/fulls/BigCherry.jpg&quot; class=&quot;fit image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;@BigCherry™️ since 2016&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/fulls/innovate48.jpg&quot; class=&quot;fit image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;@Innovation48, X-lab&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;with-my-love&quot;&gt;With My Love&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/fulls/love1.jpg&quot; class=&quot;fit image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/fulls/love.jpg&quot; class=&quot;fit image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dropbox.com/s/ttfodam5h263nx9/1000.mp4?dl=0&quot;&gt;Click to eat sugar&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/fulls/love4.png&quot; class=&quot;fit image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/fulls/love5.png&quot; class=&quot;fit image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Li Annan</name><email>lian16@mails.tsinghua.edu.com</email></author><summary></summary></entry></feed>
